

RAHUL MEHNDIRATTA

Web Developer & Programmer



GET IN TOUCH WITH ME

Cell: +91-7997167670

Email: f20171479@hyderabad.bits-

pilani.ac.in

Website: https://rahulmehndiratta2602.gi thub.io/Portfolio-Website/src/index.html

Facebook: @Rahul Mehendiratta Instagram: @mehndiratta_rahul Github: @rahul Mehndiratta 2602 Linked In: @RAHUL MEHNDIRATTA

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Got Selected for National Defence Academy-136
- Grabbed 2nd place in Chess State Level competition in VII standard .
- -Grabbed 5215 rank in IIT-JEE 2017

PROFESSIONAL BACKGROUND

I have been studying web development since 6 months and I develop in both javascript and PHP, though I primarily use javascript. I am experienced in both front and back-end development, and I am proficient in HTML/HTML5, CSS/CSS3, SASS, JavaScript, jQuery, MERN stack to name a few. I am also proficient in many non-web-based languages, including but not limited to Java,Python and C++.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Bubble Developer

FanAssists | July2021 - Current

-Developed the UI for non-disclosive software used in fantasy football analytics using bubble tool.

Service Analyst Intern

APHRDI | June 2019 - September 2019

- -Performed a research that evaluated the problems and viability of 1035 MeeSeva e-governance kiosks in the districtof Visakhapatnam.
- Used Data Analytics to provide some keen insights to resolve the major issues in the viability of these Mee-Seva centers

PREVIOUS EDUCATION

• BITS Pilani, Hyderabad Campus

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science, graduating in 2021

- -Secured 5.7 GPA
- $\hbox{-StuCCan}\, of\, Department\, of\, Sponsorship\, and\, Marketing (DOSM)\\$

• Army Public School, Ambala Cantt

Senior Secondary Education, completed in 2016

- Secured 95%
 - Rishikul Vidyapeeth Public School, Sonipat

Secondary Education, completed in 2014 -Secured 10 CGPA

SKILLS ACQUIRED

- NodeJs
- ReactJs
- Mongodb
- ExpressJs
- Javascript
- HTML/CSS
- Java(Beginner)
- Python(Beginner)
- C/C++
- Bubble
- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- OOPS
- DS

PROJECTS

• **Pixel-FireNotes** September 2018-February 2019

An automated application is proposed and intended to develop in order to keep track of the regular activities and aid people in managing the daily home inventories.

Repository:

https://github.com/rahulMehndiratta2602/Pixel-FireNotes

• Classification Algorithms October 2020-February 2021

This repository contains python from scratch implementation of 6 ML classification algorithms without using ML libraries like sklearn and only using python libraries like numpy and pandas.

Repository:

https://github.com/rahulMehndiratta2602/Machine-Learning

Flipkart Clone

Present

This clone website of flipkart is under development and is expected to be completed by December 2021 Repository:

https://github.com/rahulMehndiratta2602/FlipkartClone

CHECKOUT MY DESIGNS

- https://rahulmehndiratta2602.github.io/Easybank-Landing-page/src/index.html
- https://rahulmehndiratta2602.github.io/Website-Designs/Moonlight/index.html
- https://rahulmehndiratta2602.github.io/Website-Designs/Jungle/src/index.html